Guide to the Center for Housing and Environmental Studies records, 1950-1969.
Center for Housing and Environmental Studies records
- "Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous, 1950-1952, 1950, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 3A-B)
  T.S. and M.C. carbon correspondence, memos, reports
- Housing Research Center - Housing Research Council of the Building Research Advisory Board, 1950-1955 (Box 10, Folder 4A-B)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, survey reports, pamphlets
- Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous Volume II, 1953, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 5A-B)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, M.C. memo, blueprints, pamphlets
- Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous, 1954, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  T.S. carbon statement, correspondence
- Housing Research Center Miscellaneous Volume II, 1955, 1954, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Carbon abstracts, M.C. report
- Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous, Volume I, 1955, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8A-B)
  M.C. draft, T.S. and carbon correspondence
- Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous, Volume III, January - June 1956, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 9A-B)
  T.S> carbon correspondence, memo, pamphlets
- Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous, Volume IV, July - December 1956, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, memo
- Housing Research Center - Miscellaneous, Volume V, January 1957 onwards, 1956, 1957, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Survey, T.S and carbon correspondence, memo, drafts
- 1959 - 1960 Housing Research Center, 1959, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  T.S. and carbon M.C. correspondence, articles
- Housing Research Center, January 1958 - January 1960, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  T.S. proposals, correspondence, memo budget request, M.C. outline
- Housing Research center, Law of housing and Urban Redevelopment, 1951, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  T.S. and carbon M.S. correspondence, proposal
- Visual Aids Photos (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Photographs
- Pictures - Beyer, Loberg, Mackesey, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- "To Glenn Beyer (from) Visual Aid, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Photographs, negatives
- Exterior A Design (Etc.) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Negatives
- - (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Envelope (5.5x7.5), negative
- Projection Table - Single Page (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Negative
- 6.co. Study Picture of Dilapidation (Box 11, Folder 7)
- "Look Pictures" (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Photos - Cornell Kitchen, 1955, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Photographs with descriptions
- Campus Mail to Beyer (Box 11, Folder 10)
- "Top Professor Marilyn Langford", 1961 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Negatives, photographs
- Campus Mail to Glenn Beyer (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Color photographs (Enlargements)
- "R-S" (Box 11, Folder 13)
- "B+C" (Box 11, Folder 14)
- "A (Interiors)" (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Department of Housing and Design (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Fundamentals of Housing (Box 11, Folder 17A)
  Microfilm
- Lustron (Box 11, Folder 17B)
- Picture Prints, 1949, 1950, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Negatives, photographs, correspondence
- 1957 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- 1958 Photographs, 1959, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Photos - Houses, Exteriors, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Photographs, correspondence
- "Cornell Kitchen - Good Pictures, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Cornell Kitchen - Poor Photographs (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Unidentified Photograph, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  Photograph, correspondence
- Cornell Kitchen - Family Trip Records, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  Carbon T.S. correspondence, M.S. correspondence, reports
- No 8 Kitchen Correspondence, 1949, 1951-1954 (Box 11, Folder 26A-B)
  Carbon T.S. correspondence, M.S. correspondence, blueprints, photographs
- Kitchen - Miscellaneous, Volume III, 1955-1956, 1955, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  T.S. and M.S. correspondence, pamphlets
- No 8 Drawings and Sketches Cornell Kitchen, 1953, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  Correspondence, drawings, sketches
- Condolences of Morton J. Schussheim, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Correspondence Resulting from Sabbatical trip abroad, 1962, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, M.S. postcards
- Forest Park Foundation, Application for Grant 1962, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  T.S. carbon correspondence
- Progressive Copenhagen Trip, August 1963, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, M.C. information
- "Proposal for Action to Governor Nelson A Rockefeller, Members of the Faculty, Cornell University, Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty, New York, 1966, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Statements, correspondence
- Personal - Venezuela Working Papers, 1960, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Memos, reports, P.C. correspondence, M.S. notes, map, pamphlet
- Venezuela Correspondence, May 1961, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, lists, travel information, vitae
- Speeches - 1960, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 7A-B)
  Memos, correspondence, papers, pamphlets
- Speeches, 1957-1959, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  M.S. carbon correspondence, carbon M.C. talks, news releases
- Speeches - Glenn H. Beyer, 1948-1953, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 9A-B)
  Memoirs, reports, talks
- Articles, 1959-1963 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, articles
- Articles, 1948-1959 (Box 12, Folder 11A-B)
- Housing: A Factual Analysis Book, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 12A-B)
- 1963 Housing: A Factual Analysis Revision", 1957, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 13A-B)
  T.S. Carbon correspondence, pamphlets
- 1960 Census Technical Papers, Beyer, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Summary papers, correspondence
- Bureau of the Census, Housing Census Advisory Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, travel documents, reports
- Prefab Research Project, Housing Research Center, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, drafts, T.S. notes
- Prefab Volume II, 1955, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- De Meo Construction Correspondence and Plans, 1958, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, M.S. notes, sketches, blueprints
- Housing Conference 1960, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  T.S. carbon memos, correspondence, pamphlets
- Measurement of housing Quality Summary Sheets, G. Price, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Summaries, maps
- Prefab Study, Volume III, 1956-1957, 1955, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- American Institute of Architects, 191959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, papers, reports
- Research Foundation for the American Home, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, pamphlets, reports
- Community Study, 1956-1957, 1955-1958 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- America is Expanding Met. Fringes, Faculty Discussion Group, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Memos, lists, correspondence
- Surplus Metropolitan Fringe Memos and Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  M.C. memos, papers, carbon minutes, pamphlet
- Burea of the Census Farm Housing Monograph Vouchers, 1953-1956 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Correspondence, vouchers
- "Bureau of the Census, Farm Housing Monograph Miscellaneous, 1952-1958 (Box 13, Folder 15A-B)
  Correspondence, monograph
- "Project Statements Inactive", 1947-1958 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, statements, memos
- "Committee on 9ths and 12ths, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  M.C. memos, drafts, carbon memos
- Graduate File, 1956-1957, 1957-1958, 1958-1959, 1948, 1950, 1952-1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  T.S., M.S. carbon correspondence, M.C. and carbon memos, lists
- Architecture - Research Position for 1959-1960, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  T.S., carbon, M.S. correspondence
- Graduate Assistants and Some Graduate Students in HD Research, 1952, 1955 - 1959 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, memos
- 1960 Census, National Conference on Housing Census, 1956, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  M.C. memos, census summary
- Bureau of the Census, Evaluation of Condition Group, 1957, 1958, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  M.C. reports, notes, T.S. correspondence
- Farm and home Week, 1956, 1957, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Correspondence, memos, pamphlets
- HRC - Proposal to Study Distribution Costs of Building Materials (Box 13, Folder 24)
  T.S. carbon correspondence, proposals